Really?
Yes, mom, I have to go.  [screaming]
So I'm going to Mumbai to do a
collab with the YouTubers.  I started making videos on YouTube in 2020
and look,
in 2026, YouTube people finally
called me to Mumbai.  Look, now I am going to Mumbai for three-four days.
So
a lot of preparations have to be done brother.  Packing almost
done.  Nels Dunn.  But friend, what about the tanning of this face
?  It must be very hot in Mumbai.  I
use this Dean face wash.
Anyway, I really liked its viral Didon face pack.
So I thought I should try its face wash also.
Come, he is coming to the courtyard.
Come.
Mom has come, she has come.  See how much care mom is taking of me today.  The
daughter is going to Mumbai.
Let's eat and drink.  Now let's see if
my face is shining or not.
Brother, you look so fresh.  Now this
face tanning has also reduced.  It seems that now
only Sejal Gaba will shine in Mumbai.  Come on
brother, run now otherwise you will be late for the flight.
So meet them.  This is my lovely
manager.  And finally I landed in the city of dreams,
Mumbai.  Well, now I have set out into the streets of Mumbai to
find Vada Pav.  See you in the
next blogs from Mumbai